<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<AboutArticle>
  <About culture="ru-ru">
    <Body>[_STRONG_]Mytrip.Mvc[_/STRONG_] CMS с открытым исходным кодом(C# MVC3 RAZOR)[_BR_][_BR_]Доп ссылки на ресурсы:[_BR_][_A href="http://mytripmvc.codeplex.com/" target=_blank_]mytripmvc.codeplex.com[_/A_][_BR_][_A href="http://code.msdn.microsoft.com/mytripmvc" target=_blank_]code.msdn.microsoft.com/mytripmvc[_/A_][_BR_]</Body>
  </About>
  <About culture="en-us">
    <Body>[_P_][_B_]Mytrip.Mvc[_/B_] (MTM) is an open source Content Management System, based on Microsoft's .NET MVC technology, which enables you to build Web sites. For now project include several modules: Users, News, Articles, Blogs, Votes and more coming soon. Every module has separated settings, which can be found in the control panel. Some of the modules can be switched on or off.[_BR_]MTM support multilingual interface and theming. You can use either Microsoft Sql Server (Sql Express) or MySQL database.[_BR_][_BR_][_B_]Features Overview[_/B_][_BR_]Here is a list of features.[_BR_][_BR_][_U_][_B_]User Management[_/B_][_/U_][_BR_]MTM has a registration system. There are four user groups with different permissions on what users are allowed to view, create, edit, and manage content. Administrator can to choose what kind of user registration to use: with or without captcha or email activation.[_BR_][_BR_][_U_][_B_]Articles Management[_/B_][_/U_][_BR_]News, Articles, Blogs.... You can choose witch module to use Articles or Blogs or both of them. Categories for articles can be inserted in the menu and showed in all languages. Users can rate articles and leave comments. Every user can create own blog after specific number of comments, which can be changed in setting. Creating content is simple with the HTML editor, giving even novice users the ability to combine text and images. Administrator can access Article Archive for latest updates and site statistic. User Profile helps to review user last activity. And more, and even more coming soon…[_BR_][_BR_][_U_][_B_]Votes[_/B_][_/U_][_BR_]Simple way to get more information from users, it’s creating votes with multiple options.[_BR_][_BR_][_U_][_B_]File Manager[_/B_][_/U_][_BR_]The File Manager is the tool for easily managing files or folders. The File Manager is integrated into the Article Editor so you can grab images and other files at any time. Also Administrator has full access to all files and folder from site directory.[_/P_]</Body>
  </About>
</AboutArticle>